Against the Night is a horror, thriller, mystery
film directed by Brian Cavallaro.
A group of friends sneak into an abandoned prison with the intention of making a
ghost hunting video, until they start to go missing one by one.
Detective Ramsey, played by Frank Whaley.
Rachel, played by Hannah Kleeman.
Sean, played by Tim Torre.
Hank, played by Luke Persiani.
Dan, played by Josh Cahn.
Brooke, played by Nicole Souza.
Against the Night (also known as Amityville Prison) is a 2017 American
horror film written and directed by Brian Cavallaro.
A limited theatrical release starring Hannah Kleeman, Tim Torre, and Frank Whaley, it is premised around a group of
friends who start being killed one by one while shooting a ghost hunting video in Holmesburg Prison.
The film explores themes of handheld camera, ghost hunting,
prison visit, old building, trapped in building.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.